

CONTACT

- 363/C/1, Pirerbag, Mirpur 2
- m3alamin@gmail.com
- Website github.com/m3alamin
- Phone +(880) 1716 400 403

EXPERTISE

Laravel Framework (PHP, MySQL)

ReactJS

Node.JS

Django Framework (Python)

Docker, AWS, Flask, CakePHP

REFERENCES

Mamunur Rahman Hera

Sr. Software Engineer

T: + (880) 1933 853 750

E: hera@w3engineers.com

Rezwanul Shiplu

Sr. Software Engineer

T: + (880) 1705 110 917

E: shiplu@ryansplus.com

MD AL AMIN

Software Developer



PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Experienced tech professional working in Laravel, ReactJS, NodeJS. Individual software developer with strong analytical & problem solving skills with 7+ years experience in development. Offering outstanding ability to work with various programming languages, including PHP, JavaScript, Python.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Ryans IT Ltd.

Sr. Software Engineer

November, 2019 to Continuing

Working in Laravel based eCommerce application development.

API development using Laravel

UI/UX using ReactJS

W3engineers Ltd.

Software Developer

November, 2016 - November 2019

Developing and maintaining REST API using Laravel, NodeJS, Python.

Developing NodeJs, Express, MongoDB based applications.

Website Solutions Ltd.

Software Developer

September, 2012 - October, 2016

Developed Laravel and CakePHP based application.

Developed PHP and JavaScript based applications.

Developed Magento based eCommerce shops.



EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science & Engineering

Dhaka International University

2008-2012

